# Bradley Cameron Pick

Email: bcpick1995@gmail.com

Mobile: 07861104662

Website | LinkedIn Account | GitHub Account (Portfolio)

### Personal Profile

An incredibly motivated programming graduate flexible and open to different fields within the tech industry while also mainly focused on web development. Having been employed for four years at my current job, originally starting as a post-graduate internship, I have greatly expanded my knowledge of core web development skills as well as adapting to modern web development technologies and frameworks.

### Achievements

- Four years of working in web development on a permanent basis.
- Working in a start-up has enabled me to understand how to build up a company, and the product, from essentially scratch and has proved an invaluable experience.
- Despite not necessarily coming from a web development background I have been able to adapt and prove myself, as well as becoming a significant contributor to the team.
- Assisting in upgrading a codebase from Angular JS to Angular 12 which at the time was approximately over five thousand lines of code.

## Education

# **Birmingham City University 2013-2017 BSc (hons) in Computer Games Technology 2:1** Key Modules:

- Computer Systems Technology
- Computer Networks and Distributions
- Open Systems
- Mobile and Web Technology I
- Mobile and Web Technology II

Final Year Project: Exploring the user of Model Driven Development to develop a Final Year Project.

#### Wrenn School (2006 – 2013)

- Achieved A-Levels in ICT, English Literature and English Language.
- 14 GCSEs A-C, including Mathematics and English.

### **Employment**

Front End Web Developer | Semantic Audio Labs Ltd. (2018 – Present)

Key duties includes:

- Developing a Digital Audio Workstation (DAW) using core web development skills.
  - Specifically, HTML5, JS and the Angular framework (currently version 12, originally AngularJS) and CSS (as well as LESS and SASS).
  - Furthermore, other more niche technologies like the PUG template engine have been used.
  - Some usage of PHP to fix some issues.
- An understanding of NodeJS and NPM, as well as being able to set up and use a proxy to be able to test changes locally.
- Responding to feature requests and implementing these requests usually from scratch.
- Working with a team using modern GIT and CMS technologies (GitLab, Sourcetree as a GUI for Git) to ensure a good workflow, as well as dealing with issues, setting sprints etc.
  - o For instance, we had close to 2000 merge requests created in our main repository.
- Fixing issues reported by users using the aforementioned CMS.
  - I personally have authored 584 merge requests that were successfully merged (in our main repository), as well as reviewing and merging 347 requests of my coworkers.
- Being involved in weekly meetings relating to current sprints, responding to feedback and planning out methodologies to meet current goals.
- Integrating Google Sign-In as well as a forum (Discourse).
- Assisting new colleagues in becoming familiar with the code base.

Website: https://alpha.faders.io

### Web Develop / Designer | Paragon Property Maintenance Ltd. (2016; July 2017 – August 2017)

Key duties included:

- Successfully designed a website for the client using HTML5, CSS and JavaScript.
- Listening to the client's requests and feedback and creating a website that matched the brief.
- Utilised some backend PHP to create a webform.
- Tested and ensured the website worked successfully, verifying with the client. Also maintained and reworked the website afterwards following subsequent feedback.
- Ensured the website worked on various media devices (i.e.: desktop PC, mobile.)

Website: <a href="https://paragonpropertymaintenance.co.uk/">https://paragonpropertymaintenance.co.uk/</a>

# Hobbies and Interests

In my free time I do like to indulge in gaming (in particular Nintendo) and various gaming projects, such as fan games and modifications. This includes both playing and developing them. I find this a fun use of my time, as well as being able to use programming languages I wouldn't usually use in web development such as C if developing using the Unity engine. Outside of that, I enjoy socialising with friends, including going to the cinema (my favourite genre is probably horror), visiting new places and meeting new people. Finally, for fun each holiday I would incorporate fun themes into the DAW (such as a winter mode featuring falling snow) in my spare time; this was positively received by both users and upper management.